

CONTACTS



+8801708-591898



muzahidislam15@gmail.com



muzahidulislam.me

SKILLS

- Brand Design
- System Design
- Logo Design
- Visual Design
- Brainstorming
- UX Design

INTERESTS

- Business Design
- Research
- Traveling

MUZAHIDUL ISLAM

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm Muzahidul. I have been working as a graphic design professional for over six years now. I am a hard worker, flexible, co-operative, good in manners, and very professional in my profession, I've worked with 40+ individuals, companies, and non-profit organizations on bringing their ideas to reality through development. I would love to collaborate with you on your next project!

Program Experience: Adobe Illustrator \cdot Adobe Photoshop \cdot Adobe XD \cdot Figma \cdot Adobe After Effect \cdot Android Studio

Language: Python • Javascript • PHP • HTML • CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016-2020 Lead Graphic Designer | The ICT Hub

4 years I have been working for four years in this company as a graphic

designer & brand designer. I love the working environment here, and my colleagues are very supportive and cooperative.

Currently, I am working here on a full-time basis.

2015-2016 Graphic Designer | Hexapixel Studio

1 year Hexapixel Studio is a visual graphic studio with high morality

and good reputations. I have worked for them as a lead application developer for one year. It was a good experience, and I

have learned a lot from this work environment.

2014-2015 Lead Application Developer | Erpor Amrai LTD.

1 year Erpor Amrai LTD. is a digital marketing agency that runs adver-

tisements, promotions, and marketing for various service providers and stakeholders. I had enjoyed and learned a lot

from this company.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering

United International University

United City, Madani Avenue, Badda, Dhaka 1212, angladesh.

AWARD & CERTIFICATIONS

Participant

National Hackathon 2016

Organized by ICT Division, People's Republic of Bangladesh

Finalist

Tech for Peace 2017

Organized by Preneur Labs & Democracy International Bangladesh